<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.236">Family background... If I were to sum it up in a word very confused, I was moved around a lot because my mum had</p>
      <p begin="00:00:17.592">domestic violence from my dad. I didn’t really have much of a childhood in the sense of the luxury things of being a child</p>
      <p begin="00:00:29.793">because my mum was a single parent and there was me and my sister... I am one of 9, my dad’s got, I’ve got family in Jamaica</p>
      <p begin="00:00:43.568">I’ve got a brother in Jamaica, I’ve got a brother and sister in Bristol and I’ve got 2 sisters and a brother in another area in Gloucester</p>
      <p begin="00:00:51.353">but I’ve only got one blood sister in a sense from my mum. My mum did work, she’s always had a mixture of jobs cleaning,</p>
      <p begin="00:00:59.603">to being a care assistant for residential homes. I also remember my dad also coming to the house and my mum had to ring up my mum’s</p>
      <p begin="00:01:09.984">boyfriend at the time saying my dad’s just turned up here and he’s kicking off and he wants to take the kids and things like that</p>
      <p begin="00:01:16.703">so I remember all those things. And also for my sister as well, she tried covering up a lot of things to my mum about me because</p>
      <p begin="00:01:26.399">I was the man of the house and I was never violent to my sister physically but I was always verbal and I said</p>
      <p begin="00:01:33.107">if you tell mum I’m doing this or where I keep that watch what happens and things like that so I put a lot of heartache</p>
      <p begin="00:01:39.853">into my sister as well. I also brought a lot of heartache to my mum in the sense of when I got into drugs the police kicking off the door,</p>
      <p begin="00:01:50.766">once I got involved in an incident with drugs and I had to get a gun and stuff and armed police kicking off the door and things like that</p>
      <p begin="00:02:03.217">and I remember those things that I know were bad and I’m always saying to my mum sorry, sorry and she says don’t say that</p>
      <p begin="00:02:14.420">look at you now, you know what I mean she stuck by me, she stuck by me, she stuck by me going down the cells, going</p>
      <p begin="00:02:20.967">to court, even paying off some of my debts with drug dealers when I got out of drug selling and became more of an addict...</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>