<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.147">Work-wise? Background, background could influence work-wise I mean it took me 2 years just to get a cleaning job, I’d actually go and see</p>
      <p begin="00:00:08.989">jobs advertised in stores, in shops, go fill it out then I’d get a letter saying oh we haven’t got any jobs at the minute</p>
      <p begin="00:00:17.215">literally walk in there the week after and the advertisement is still there and it was down to name on the paper, my name isn’t</p>
      <p begin="00:00:25.505">like a John Smith but yeah I would say that sort of held me back a bit because of that.  I even had some friends, some African friends,</p>
      <p begin="00:00:37.453">that had English names and they were told you know their parents gave them English names on purpose for that reason because</p>
      <p begin="00:00:42.712">they could see in hindsight whereas I never understood at the time but now I can see why yeah so but yeah I would say that held me back a bit.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:51.855">I do have that day where I do like give up after the first hurdle, it’s the second day I start picking myself up and it is down to</p>
      <p begin="00:01:01.385">people saying small things like “you know you’ve got to try again?” or “you know you are good at it?” and I do take those things on board</p>
      <p begin="00:01:08.917">and they will stick with me and I will try again so yeah again having a good family and surrounding yourself with good people</p>
      <p begin="00:01:15.565">to keep telling you, to encourage you, to do better it’s no different to when I tried to go for promotion with the fire fighting job</p>
      <p begin="00:01:23.055">2 years ago and I was sort of, I sort of failed it, well I wouldn&apos;t say failed it, I didn’t pass it, and I was there questioning myself</p>
      <p begin="00:01:35.159">“look am I really good for the job?” and people would say “no you’ve got to keep trying” so that’s what I’m doing again I’m going for it at this minute in time.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>