<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.076">Life outside of work...  To be honest I would say it&apos;s a positive thing, I mean my family are proud, my friends are proud; I am also a DJ as well</p>
      <p begin="00:00:12.452">so doing the shifts it sort of helps me because I get a lot of time off at the same time, well rest periods I should put it,</p>
      <p begin="00:00:20.847">so no it doesn’t really affect me in a negative way if anything it’s in a positive way because I do 2 things with my life that I both enjoy.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:30.725">I mean you know I drive a nice car and stuff like that, I mean kids come up to me “that’s that DJ money” I’m like “no it’s Fire Fighter money”</p>
      <p begin="00:00:37.449">to make them see that you know you go for something like that it can get you places so in that respect I’d say that’s the best decision</p>
      <p begin="00:00:44.346">I’ve made and that is, I get more satisfaction in that than even saving people it’s the reaction I get just being in the community</p>
      <p begin="00:00:53.852">they sort of hold me with high regard and I do feel proud for it.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:59.601">Obviously I’ve got to be careful what I do on the outside of my job I mean for instance I came off a motorbike a few years ago</p>
      <p begin="00:01:08.353">and that took me out of my job for about 6 or 7 months so that had a huge impact I mean I was still able to do alternative duties</p>
      <p begin="00:01:16.029">but it did leave me to worry, you know, what would happen if it had been much worse?  So yeah I don’t know it can be a scary question</p>
      <p begin="00:01:24.698">but maybe that’s just how I think, I think if something was to stop me from doing my job health-wise as in an injury or even fitness</p>
      <p begin="00:01:34.952">straight away I’d think “have I still got a job?” when really I should be thinking, I should make adjustments but that’s just</p>
      <p begin="00:01:41.700">how I think so, no, health-wise I just try and keep to tune really.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>