<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.205">It started up from when I was at school, I was in my final year I’d done my GCSEs, left school to get a summer job and went to work</p>
      <p begin="00:00:12.610">for a company that did this sort of work and found I really enjoyed it and it was nice I wasn’t at school any more and I was meant to</p>
      <p begin="00:00:21.636">go back and do my A-Levels and I never went back and I just followed that line...  I suppose it was an escape from school in a way</p>
      <p begin="00:00:29.642">which although I was quite good at I didn’t really like, I went through a period of wanting to join the RAF but for some reason</p>
      <p begin="00:00:38.893">I didn’t go down that line so yes I found it interesting and so I followed that line and then went, took some guidance to go to college</p>
      <p begin="00:00:51.418">and get my training as it wasn’t just going into a job without any training and went from there really and progressed from an apprentice</p>
      <p begin="00:01:02.613">up to moving up the ladder to finally actually the company we worked for my father worked for as well and it went into liquidation</p>
      <p begin="00:01:15.617">well they closed down they’d had enough of that particular business and we took it on from then.  I suppose I enjoyed that it wasn’t</p>
      <p begin="00:01:26.968">the same thing every day it wasn’t a repetition and I enjoyed the problem solving aspect of it and ways to get around a problem</p>
      <p begin="00:01:38.511">that I’ve thought of myself rather than a set pattern of things to follow i.e. if you’re working on a production line or something</p>
      <p begin="00:01:47.671">you just picked product A, B and C I mean it was always a problem solving type of job and also the interaction with lots of different people.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>