<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.445">I wanted to do this kind of work because it’s always appealed to me really being in an office, I’ve sort of seen it on TV and, you know, my mum’s</p>
      <p begin="00:00:08.544">always worked in this kind of environment and a few other family members and things they’ve said sort of made me think oh yeah I’d quite like to do that</p>
      <p begin="00:00:14.978">or I could do that and I think you just get to dress smartly and I think where I’ve always been quite organised as well it’s something where</p>
      <p begin="00:00:24.530">I can put that to good use organising my workload and things.  And being able to sort of mix with different kinds of people, it allows you to do that</p>
      <p begin="00:00:35.328">and it’s sort of more computer-based and that’s what I like to do really.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:40.313">I do enjoy the most being around the people I work with because they’re a great bunch, I enjoy meeting new people as well,</p>
      <p begin="00:00:47.314">I enjoy getting on with tasks, sort of throwing myself into it and being set a task and maybe doing it a different way or learning something new</p>
      <p begin="00:00:57.388">from it and being able to design spreadsheets and things like that for different things to store data.  It’s just so varied that’s what I like</p>
      <p begin="00:01:05.914">so much about the job you can just get on with so many different things it’s not just one sort of set dead-end thing that you do every day</p>
      <p begin="00:01:11.636">which can get quite tedious and boring it’s just you can be on the phone, you can be typing things up, you can be sort of moving around the office,</p>
      <p begin="00:01:19.389">helping people, meeting new people, yeah that’s what I enjoy about it.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>