<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.476">Family background... Parents are from Jamaica so I think you’d class me as like the first generation British or whatever you want to say.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:09.891">Background-wise I was brought up in a very, very strict background full of Jamaican culture, Rastafarian culture as well;</p>
      <p begin="00:00:20.768">my mum she was a nurse before she had, I think it was after my brother, after me she gave that up to take care of her family</p>
      <p begin="00:00:32.226">because she’s a mother of like 9...  So that’s, you know, but she now does community work now as well, she goes back to like Social Working</p>
      <p begin="00:00:41.188">and stuff now that the younger one is now 21.  My dad he runs an information culture centre that gives advice about the religion and also</p>
      <p begin="00:00:52.942">offers community support.  You know brought up in an inner city area there was loads of kids doing all different bad stuff and wrong stuff</p>
      <p begin="00:01:00.201">and I was around it but I was never scared of the repercussions, I was never scared of going to jail, I had friends who’d gone to jail,</p>
      <p begin="00:01:07.252">cousins who’d gone to jail and back so I was never scared of that, what scared me the most was going back and knowing the repercussions</p>
      <p begin="00:01:14.897">I’d get from my parents so I would say they were definitely the biggest influence on where I am now and my logical thinking as well</p>
      <p begin="00:01:22.488">they same advice they gave me and I’ll give to my son and it’s the same way I sort of live my life, the outlook I have,</p>
      <p begin="00:01:29.382">so yeah if it wasn’t for them it probably wouldn’t, they were like my parents and counsel at the same time without just being parents.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>