<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.000">My parents, my mum’s always been an accountant, my dad’s, it’s a strange thing, my dad’s always been working with people with disabilities;</p>
      <p begin="00:00:11.217">he did go off and do other things, he did strangely enough, he was a security guard for a little bit but that wasn’t what he wanted to do;</p>
      <p begin="00:00:18.437">he knew what to expect with cerebral palsy like it’s down one side, the balance/coordination thing so yeah he knew what I could do</p>
      <p begin="00:00:28.934">and what I could possibly do because during the ‘80s they didn’t know much about people with cerebral palsy, they were always thrown away</p>
      <p begin="00:00:36.042">or treated as &quot;special&quot;, yeah, so he knew what to look for.  When I was born with cerebral palsy the doctors used to give me pills</p>
      <p begin="00:00:47.841">and basically I was a vegetable in a wheelchair, when I came off the meds I couldn’t feed myself, couldn’t clothe myself,</p>
      <p begin="00:00:56.025">couldn’t even talk so my dad always taught me to walk, talk, that sort of thing.  Yeah and when I got older my brother took me out in my wheelchair</p>
      <p begin="00:01:12.253">my family has been very supportive, yeah, we’ve experienced a lot of things together, yeah.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:19.114">With my disability they always push me to do sit-down jobs but again I am quite stubborn and quite headstrong I always want to do</p>
      <p begin="00:01:29.535">something different and always do something different and challenge myself and when I said “I’m bored with retail work”, even though I did enjoy it,</p>
      <p begin="00:01:41.091">“I want to be a security guard or try to be a security guard”, my dad was like “you can’t do that, you’ll be on your feet all day”</p>
      <p begin="00:01:52.676">or something like... But I’m not so yeah but my mum would say “if you want to do it, do it” so and “if you fall down at least you know”</p>
      <p begin="00:02:03.064">you know if you go for something and it falls down flat well at least you’re going for it because you sit there and you go I can’t do that</p>
      <p begin="00:02:11.174">so and life slips you by but yeah...</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>