<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.431">I did a lot of different training so I started off by leaving school with just 4 GCSEs, I then went on to do a National Diploma in Performing Arts.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:10.113">When I became an administrator I worked my way up and did Level 1, 2, 3 in Customer Care and Business and Admin</p>
      <p begin="00:00:23.268">and then obviously went back to do an evening course to retrain as a beauty therapist and then gained my qualification there as well.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:33.934">I do like training and I’ll always look at other things that I can do because I think it just makes you feel more confident and</p>
      <p begin="00:00:43.130">you can never learn too much it’s always good to know more but also all three things that I’ve trained in are</p>
      <p begin="00:00:56.762">totally different so it’s good because obviously without my customer service and business admin I don’t think I’d be as confident</p>
      <p begin="00:01:05.582">and you know get on with people as much as I do if I didn’t do that. I think the most difficult one was the beauty qualification</p>
      <p begin="00:01:18.417">because the previous qualifications that I was doing I didn’t really have any other commitments but obviously I was working</p>
      <p begin="00:01:31.570">full time, I’ve got my own house and so I was doing an evening class to retrain as a beautician and it was just a lot harder</p>
      <p begin="00:01:42.736">because you don’t get the time to put in as I did when I was younger at college you know that was all I was doing 3 days a week</p>
      <p begin="00:01:50.669">was a Performing Arts National Diploma so it’s so easy and I thought it was a walk in the park compared to learning all about</p>
      <p begin="00:02:01.079">and what you don’t realise as well with a beauty therapist you have to go into all the science side of it so all the muscles and bones</p>
      <p begin="00:02:09.372">which you know you don’t really think of that when you think of a beautician you just think make-up, tanning...</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>