<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.432">I just feel very, very blessed that I’ve got a lovely partner, a strong family, immediate family, I’ve got some loyal friends now,</p>
      <p begin="00:00:09.371">I lost a lot of friends when I got out of the streets, I was called a lot of names “oh you sell-out you’re not like you used to be”.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:17.614">If people say to me “how do you feel?” I just feel happy do you know what I mean? I just feel when people say to me</p>
      <p begin="00:00:25.287">I’m not rich, I’m not poor, I’m just happy do you know what I mean? I couldn’t go out and buy a 5 or 10 grand car</p>
      <p begin="00:00:34.969">if I wanted to at the moment or I couldn’t go out and book a round the world holiday but I can save for it;</p>
      <p begin="00:00:42.628">people say “Del you’re going to be a real good dad” and I’m like “why?” and “it’s because of what you do for a job”.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:47.589">And I’m like “well OK hopefully I can inspire my children but they might be like do you know what, I respect what you do dad</p>
      <p begin="00:00:55.114">and mum but do you know what I want to be a gang banger”. So as much as people say “you’re going to be brilliant”</p>
      <p begin="00:01:00.788">I would like to think that I’m going to be a good parent.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:03.614">Mountain biking, I do a lot of off-road mountain biking, not as much as I would like to; running, that’s my real big...</p>
      <p begin="00:01:13.970">my mates call me the “Black Forest Gump”. Yeah I love road running, that’s my massive de-stress and just spending time</p>
      <p begin="00:01:24.881">with my partner, she works for a charity called Winston’s Wish, one of the biggest UK charities for bereavement, she’s</p>
      <p begin="00:01:32.421">a practitioner so she works with like all military families and stuff like that. Yeah, family time, every now and again</p>
      <p begin="00:01:40.137">might go out to the pub with the boys have a few...</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>