<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.437">I think for me from the age of sort of 15 when I was permanently excluded from Sandford School I sort of realised I was</p>
      <p begin="00:00:09.689">severely dyslexic, I thought at the time I was a young black gangsta so to speak, I didn’t really have anybody in my life</p>
      <p begin="00:00:17.512">as a positive role model apart from my mum but I never had any male influence in my life so I felt at that time the way forward</p>
      <p begin="00:00:26.954">for me was just to be a gang banger, I thought well I’m going to be like my uncles and my cousins who were driving around</p>
      <p begin="00:00:33.188">in their nice 30 grand cars with their nice bracelets and nice chains and stuff so I thought that’s the life for me so from the age</p>
      <p begin="00:00:40.756">of 15 up to the age of 21 I just thought yeah that’s what I did, I sold drugs, I took drugs, I had a little time in prison</p>
      <p begin="00:00:52.892">not for drug dealing but for violence so yeah I never really had any positive role models but then at the same time I had</p>
      <p begin="00:01:05.037">my cousins and my uncles who I did look up as role models at that time in my life whereas now I feel sorry for them because</p>
      <p begin="00:01:12.768">they’re still in that lifestyle but as you know in the game of drugs you’re there for a certain time and then one day you just</p>
      <p begin="00:01:21.219">have to hang it up and be like “do you know what it’s not me no more” and they’re still trying to be like that so, what, 15 years on</p>
      <p begin="00:01:26.516">of me turning around my life they’re still trying to be that young, bad boy.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:31.846">I had influences in my life who came into my life like my youth workers and my few peers coming to me and saying</p>
      <p begin="00:01:38.460">“look Del you need to stop doing that” and whatever but it just went in one ear and out the other because they weren’t consistent</p>
      <p begin="00:01:43.857">in my life they were just people who’d come in every now and again or if they see me in town they were like “tell me what you’re up to,</p>
      <p begin="00:01:49.411">are you still doing what you were doing?” and I’m like “no, no, no I’m giving it up” and whatever but no I wasn’t I just told them</p>
      <p begin="00:01:54.998">what they wanted to hear so at that time I’d become a bit of a conscious young male but then I’d go back to what I was doing</p>
      <p begin="00:02:02.462">10 minutes after when my phone rang and I was meeting a punter or whatever so yeah I never really had anybody to</p>
      <p begin="00:02:10.467">sort of influence me massively, no.</p>
      <p begin="00:02:15.199">I know I am different to a lot of my other black associate friends, do you know what I mean, I know I am and they say it all the time</p>
      <p begin="00:02:24.266">like “you don’t talk like a black man, you don’t walk like a black man, you don’t act like a black man” how should I be acting?</p>
      <p begin="00:02:30.568">Society says so that I should be, what, wearing my trousers half way down my arse? Having all sovereigns on my fingers?</p>
      <p begin="00:02:37.316">Having a big chain? Having a bandana hanging out my butt? Come on we’re in the 20th Century for God’s sake and like they hear</p>
      <p begin="00:02:44.315">what I’m saying, they do, I know they do, but it’s better for them to be stubborn and be like “do you know Del’s right but I’m not going to tell him...”</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>