<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.474">School didn’t suit me at all so not really, I wouldn’t say I took very much from school really; I took all I could.  It’s more after school where it sort of</p>
      <p begin="00:00:09.924">really kicked in &quot;right I need to sort my life out I need to do something&quot; so I went and did a course which gave me a Level 1 in Business Administration</p>
      <p begin="00:00:19.982">which was a good foundation for what I went on to do next which was an apprenticeship for a recruitment agency so it was still a lot of</p>
      <p begin="00:00:27.140">front of house so from quite a young age I built up quite a lot of experience meeting new people which I manage to put to use now</p>
      <p begin="00:00:34.140">and build up to Level 2 in Business Admin and then I finished that and then took a while off because I had my little girl and then</p>
      <p begin="00:00:43.919">decided I wanted to go back to work again so I went onto an Inspire project which is sort of like gaining more work experience in a work environment</p>
      <p begin="00:00:53.343">and learnt all I could from that and listened to people and just really tried to throw myself into it.  What I enjoyed the most was just not being</p>
      <p begin="00:01:05.386">in that school classroom environment I think, not having someone stood at the front of the class telling you things and having to think</p>
      <p begin="00:01:11.755">“oh gosh I don&apos;t remember any of that” there’s someone there and in a work environment you learn what you need to know to be able to</p>
      <p begin="00:01:18.154">do your job so I think I enjoy just not having to worry about doing Maths lessons or English lessons it was more sort of</p>
      <p begin="00:01:25.690">&quot;right you need to know this to be able to do your job&quot; and just learning that and then you know having a manager there to oversee things</p>
      <p begin="00:01:33.457">not just to tell you what you’re doing but to go to and say “look, sorry, I don’t understand this can you go through it again?”</p>
      <p begin="00:01:39.212">and just sort of working through it.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:42.098">To be honest I enjoyed college but I think while I was at college I wasn’t specifically doing a course I was there in my last year of school</p>
      <p begin="00:01:53.444">because I didn’t get kicked out of school but I had troubles at school so they thought it would be a more suitable place for me doing pre-16</p>
      <p begin="00:01:58.995">so I enjoyed it but I wasn&apos;t in the right frame of mind for it while I was there it was more after that I went on to do more training in admin</p>
      <p begin="00:02:09.197">when I sorted myself out mentally a bit I think that I actually enjoyed and got something out of it.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>