<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.271">The most significant turning point is a crossroads I came to when two opportunities came at the exact same time, the exact same day</p>
      <p begin="00:00:10.616">Mainstream Radio or Fire Fighter post and my heart was leading to the DJ-ing because it’s something I always wanted to do</p>
      <p begin="00:00:21.366">and the Mainstream Radio that came through was as a kid is the one that I always wanted to go for; I didn’t really see the importance of</p>
      <p begin="00:00:29.980">the Fire Fighter post at the time, I always thought the Fire Fighter post I could always go back for whenever I wanted to</p>
      <p begin="00:00:37.982">I mean I was only like 23 or 24 at the time so that was my understanding was “oh yeah, I can try that next year” but the Mainstream Radio</p>
      <p begin="00:00:44.519">you can’t try again can you?  Once if comes if that goes you know you’re out and I was nearly going to go for it but</p>
      <p begin="00:00:52.738">you know I sort of talked around, I wouldn&apos;t even say talked around where it was like I just listened to everybody else, you know</p>
      <p begin="00:01:02.110">my missis who is my wife now, she was my girlfriend at the time, said to me “what do you always think about money-wise?”</p>
      <p begin="00:01:07.670">and money-wise I still think of now is how I’m going to have that, I always want a good amount of money coming in month by month</p>
      <p begin="00:01:16.585">being able to have a pension, would the DJ-ing give me that?  No.  Would it give me the most enjoyment? Yes.  But I&apos;m always</p>
      <p begin="00:01:23.498">worrying about where the next money’s coming from but the Fire Fighter would, you know, allow me to know where I&apos;m getting</p>
      <p begin="00:01:28.708">that money from so I went with that and it’s the best decision ever since really because of the experiences I’ve had with it.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>