<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.173">My mum and my dad divorced at 12, dad moved to Wolverhampton when I was 16 because they kept on swapping</p>
      <p begin="00:00:08.275">you know we lived in a council estate and then mum would move and dad would live with us and dad would move and then</p>
      <p begin="00:00:18.020">they kept on swapping until eventually dad moved to Wolverhampton and found a girlfriend there and then obviously mum stayed</p>
      <p begin="00:00:24.671">that’s when obviously the discipline was out the house, that’s when I became all rebellious and stuff like that and you know</p>
      <p begin="00:00:32.277">my 2 sisters, they’re both younger than me... Dad really hasn’t supported me with anything that I’ve done to be honest</p>
      <p begin="00:00:40.426">like we’re just, you know, getting back to our relationship now but even when I went to Africa he was “no, don’t....”</p>
      <p begin="00:00:51.437">there was always some negativity allowed to kick in you know and even my nan and all that sort of stuff, like my family</p>
      <p begin="00:00:56.924">there was no support, you know, I never got no support like I never heard anyone say “you can do it”, “don’t give up”, none of that.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:07.832">The only thing my dad used to say “what are you going to do when you’re older?” “what do you want to be when you’re older?”</p>
      <p begin="00:01:14.872">but I think every kid’s had that talk with their parents “what do you want to be when you’re older?” “you’re wasting your life”</p>
      <p begin="00:01:20.925">you know that was it but as a career like you know there was no motivation or anything like that, nothing.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:28.246">I’m not hiding you know mum was an alcoholic you know she was a piss-head it’s what it is, you know, and I’m not...</p>
      <p begin="00:01:36.828">all that shit that’s happened with them that’s affected me but it’s made me the person who I am today a semi-professional photographer</p>
      <p begin="00:01:42.576">that still loves my mum, my dad and my sisters, you get me?</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>