<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.065">Shift-based but you turn up at 8 o’clock in the morning sort of thing and if we were doing search warrants that day, for example, we would start</p>
      <p begin="00:00:09.776">at 5am in the morning, we’d have a briefing, we’d go out, kick the doors in, arrest the individuals that we had to arrest and all the rest of it</p>
      <p begin="00:00:17.425">and then you’re processing those people throughout the day.  I never, ever finished on time, never finished on time I would ring my wife</p>
      <p begin="00:00:24.074">“I’ll be late”, “I’ll be late”, “I’ll be late” and 8 hour days often turned into 12, 15, 20 hour days that was the nature of the beast with the job, and</p>
      <p begin="00:00:33.602">the unit that we were on.  The uniform shifts are different, they work 11 hour shifts but if you’re in an investigative role which we were</p>
      <p begin="00:00:41.004">you can’t just go home and leave an individual in the cells to rot until the next day, there are rules and regulations and timeframes to adhere to</p>
      <p begin="00:00:50.157">so you know going on from that if you weren’t out on an action day like that, sort of thing, you’re catching up with paperwork or putting</p>
      <p begin="00:01:00.114">crime files together for court cases, chasing up forensic evidence or if you had a slack moment I just used to go out with a colleague</p>
      <p begin="00:01:08.220">and we’d go out looking for drug dealers and stuff like that, you’ve just got to know where to look, they’re out there, target certain phone boxes</p>
      <p begin="00:01:16.646">they always use the same ones because they’re not the brightest individuals and wait for the dealers to turn up and jump on them</p>
      <p begin="00:01:22.382">and you’re just creating jobs from nothing, no intelligence just using a little bit of savvy really.</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>