<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">

  <head>
    <styling>
    </styling>
  </head>

  <body>
    <div>
      <p begin="00:00:00.274">I’m Darren, I’m an engineer and I’m currently in a career change into sports management and coaching.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:05.774">On the engineering side I trained as an agricultural mechanic with horticultural and agricultural machinery i.e. tractors and everything else that’s</p>
      <p begin="00:00:17.926">mechanised in the agricultural field.  There could be servicing plant and machinery, repairing a breakdown if something’s</p>
      <p begin="00:00:30.642">an emergency breakdown and they need it it would be to go out in a vehicle to repair it because obviously the size of some of these</p>
      <p begin="00:00:39.428">implements they can’t bring them to you you’ve got to go to them so it could be driving 2 or 3 hours to get to somewhere</p>
      <p begin="00:00:46.221">repair it and you don’t really know what the problem is until you get there so it’s a bit of problem solving and dealing with what’s thrown at you really</p>
      <p begin="00:01:01.592">and so that’s why the timescale is you can schedule a day as in you’ve got a couple of hours to do this blah, blah, blah</p>
      <p begin="00:01:12.193">but as the day goes through the schedule will be all blown out of the water because something’s taken far longer than you imagined it would.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:19.196">Additionally as a hobby I did sports coaching but I found that was more... It personally developed myself so I then enrolled in a</p>
      <p begin="00:01:31.281">volunteer programme to help young children in sport and I found that more enriching so I’m carrying on in that vein</p>
      <p begin="00:01:38.028">and going into schools with a programme to help roll out and to teach kids movement patterns and get them off the X-box...</p>
    </div>
  </body>

</tt>